Included demo scene requires the newest versions of HDRP and Post Processing module (2.1.7 - compatybile to Unity 2018.3) to work properly. 

If the demo scene isn’t loading properly, you may need to do one or all of the following:


• “HDRenderPipelineAsset”, found in your project view, may need to be connected to the “Scriptable Render Pipeline Settings” field in the Graphics tab, under Project Settings.


• “Color Space” should be set to Linear (not Gamma) in the Player tab, under Project Settings. 